So, the wedding caterer
sent me this list
of 12 appetizers
and I have to narrow
it down to six.
Food? Gimme.
So, did Monica tell you
about this great band
called the Swing Kings
that we're trying
to get to play
for the wedding?
Since when are you
into swing music?
Since forever.
I used to go all over town
listening to bands.
Chandler...
Gap commercial.
So, did you book them?
Did you call?
I will.
Do you want me to call?
No, I'll do it.
You just stick
to your job.
What is your job?
Staying out of the way.
This is impossible,
Monica.
Why don't you just pick
all 15?
There were only 12.
Oh, yeah. I added three.
What are "peanut butter
fingers"?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Well, hello.
She's cute.
Should we go try
to talk to her?
Sure. It's one
of the great things
about being engaged.
I'm not nervous talking
to pretty girls anymore.
Could you guys help me?
( stammers )
Uh, yeah.
Let me get that for you.
It's really heavy.
( scoffs )
I got it.
( groans )
So, hi, I'm Ross
and this is
my friend Chandler.
I'm Kristen.
Kristen, hi.
Are you new to the area?
'Cause if you are
I'd love to show
you around sometime.
I actually just moved
from four blocks over.
Ah.
But this block is
like a whole other world.
Actually, it does have
a very interesting history.
This street is
the first street
in the city
to have an underground
sewer system.
Before that, sewage and
waste would just flow
right down the street.
Sometimes, ankle deep.
Smooth.
Excuse me?
Um, say, you're going
to be starving
after all this moving.
What do you say
I take you to
dinner tonight?
I'd like that.
Yeah? Great.
Let me take this
up for you.
After you.
No, no. After you.
Oh, my god!
Am I crazy
or does this totally go?
Oh, my god!
You look so beautiful!
Thank you, Rachel,
but look at Monica.
This is it.
Yep, this is the one.
I can't believe
I found it.
Wow, you look so beautiful.
If I knew you, I'd cry.
Well, I'm Monica Geller.
Bawl like a baby.
I'm Megan Bailey.
Have you found your dress yet?
Oh, no. These dresses are
all so amazing
but there is no way
I could afford one.
No, I can't afford this, either.
No. I'm just here
to figure out
which one I want.
Then I'm going
to get it at Kleinman's
this discount place
in Brooklyn.
Day after tomorrow
they're having a huge sale.
Oh, thanks for the tip.
Yeah. So when
are you getting married?
Oh, I'm not.
I just like
to try these on.
I do the same thing.
( chuckles )
I'm just kidding.
I'm getting married
July 25th.
I'm just kidding, too.
( laughs )
I'm getting married
in December.
So, when are you
getting married?
May 15th.
Ooh, it's getting close.
Yeah.
So, who's your photographer?
Jeffrey.
We met with him.
Did he show you the photos
of the nude wedding he did?
Best man? Wow.
I know. I almost called
off my wedding.
Oh, who's your band?
Oh, my fiancé wants
the Swing Kings.
Oh, you're so lucky.
My fiancé wants the
heavy metal band Carcass.
Ooh, is that spelled
with a "C" or a "K"?
Oh, my god!
It doesn't matter!
They're both great! Oh!
Oh, you know what?
Don't buy that here
Now that you know what you want
you should go to Kleinman's.
You can get it half off.
This place is overpriced.
I own this store.
So, does this come
in another color or...?
Hi.
Are you moving in or moving out?
Moving in.
Oh. Can I give you a hand?
Okay, but be careful
'cause the guy
who was helping me before
had to leave because
he hurt his back.
Boyfriend?
No.
I'm Joey.
Kristen.
Oh, wow, what a beautiful name.
What is it again?
Kristen.
Ah, that's it.
You live around here?
Yeah, yeah.
Right down there.
Listen, let me give you
a little tip.
Do not take a nap
on this stoop
or you could wake up
with your shoes gone.
I'll remember that.
Okay.
Listen, would you
like to have dinner
with me tonight?
I have plans tonight.
But how about tomorrow?
Sounds great.
Okay, all right.
Well, where does this go?
You look strong.
Why don't I take
that and you grab
one of the boxes?
Okay. Yeah.
I'll get this one.
So, this is Brooklyn.
All right
listen up.
There's usually only
one dress in each size
so when they open
those doors, fan out.
Now, this is what
you're looking for.
Memorize it.
When you locate the dress,
blow on these, all right?
Three sharp blasts.
When you hear it,
come running.
Okay. Got it.
All right.
Oh, they're pushing!
They're pushing!
Hey, don't be a baby!
Well, I don't...
Let's go!
( yells )
Hey! Rachel, come on!
No. No, not it. Not it. Not it.
Uh!
Don't crowd me!
This is it!
This is the dress!
Oh, my god. It's perfect.
I'm sorry. This one's taken.
Whoa!
Megan!
Monica!
You came!
Yeah.
This is my dress.
No.
Yes, it is.
You saw me wearing it.
And now you'll see me
buying it.
You freak!
You wouldn't have even known
about this place
if it wasn't for me.
Look, you don't want
to fight me.
Maybe I do.
I'm pretty feisty.
I'm coming! I'm coming!
( whistle blows thrice )
Okay.
( whistle blows )
Hey! What do I do?!
( whistling continues )
What are you doing?
Did you find the dress?
No. You've got to get
me out of here, Phoebe.
These bargain shoppers
are crazy!
We got to get Monica!
No, you got
to hold my hand!
Oh, my god!
( whistle continues blowing )
Excuse me!
Go! Go! Go!
Hey!
Go!
( whistling continues )
So, Ross, how was your date
the other night?
Did you tell her
about the magical ride
that starts with the flush
of every toilet?
Laugh all you want
but she actually left me
a message saying
she'd like to go out again.
In fact
I'm going to go
call her right now
and I'll make sure to tell her
my friend Chandler says...
( stammers )
Hey, Chandler.
Hey.
Listen, sorry I didn't
stop by last night
but I had a date.
Joe, when it's 1:00
in the morning
and you don't come by,
that's okay.
Check it out.
It was with this
really hot girl
who just moved in
right across the street.
Really?
Right across the street?
Yeah.
When did you meet her?
Two days ago.
Excellent.
You know,
Ross met somebody, too.
Oh, yeah?
Hey.
Hi. How'd it go?
Oh, great. We're going
out again Saturday.
But I just found out
she's also seeing
some other guy.
Really?
Joe, what would you do
if you were in Ross's situation?
I sorta am. I mean, yeah.
I'm dating this girl
who's also seeing another guy
but I'm not too worried
about it.
Well, you shouldn't be.
Believe me, I wouldn't want
to be the guy
who's up against you.
I mean, that doofus is going
to lose.
So, this is nice.
I wish I didn't have to go,
believe me.
But, unfortunately, I have to.
Oh, by the way
what's the name of the girl
you're dating?
Kristen Lang.
Bye!
Well, obviously,
only one of us
can keep dating her.
Obviously. So how
do we decide?
Well, now, let's, let's look
at this objectively.
I think I should date her.
Uh-huh, uh-huh
or, or... I'm the
one who dates her.
That's interesting,
but check this out.
I date her.
Yeah, yeah, I like that
but just to go in
another direction...
Okay, okay, this can
go on for a while.
Yeah, well, we should
order some food then.
No, Joey.
Look, why don't, why don't we
just let her decide?
Okay, hey, hey,
we'll each go out with her
one more time,
and, and we'll see
who she likes best.
That sounds fair.
Maybe I'll take her
to that new French restaurant
down the street.
Hey, wait a second, now.
Look, we're going
to have to set
a spending limit
on the date.
I don't have the money to take
her to a fancy place like that.
Well, sorry, that's
what I do on dates.
All right, well,
I guess I'll just
have to do what I do on dates.
So let's decide
on a spending limit.
Yeah.
Uh... umm...
Hmm...
and a slice...
Six dollars?
I was thinking more
like a hundred?
Okay. Can I borrow $94?
( gasps )
I know.
Could you hand
me a tissue?
( three whistle blasts )
What?
You're out of Diet Coke.
( telephone ringing )
Hello.
What?!
You what?!
Hey, you listen here, missy.
What?
Wha...?
That was that girl Megan.
She booked the Swing Kings
on the day of our wedding
and said I couldn't
have them back
unless I gave
her the dress.
( gasps )
Does that mean
Carcass is available?
What am I going to do?
That is the dress.
Well...
Chandler wants the band.
What do I do?
Figure out a way
to talk him out of it.
How?
( three whistle blasts )
You're out
of toilet paper!
( loud knocking )
Hey.
What's up?
I just wanted to come by
and wish you good
luck on your date.
Thanks.
Yeah. What time
you meeting her?
We have 8:00 reservations
at Gramercy Bistro.
That's in, like, 20 minutes.
You better get dressed.
I am dressed.
Oh. Oh, well good.
For me.
What is this?
Did you give yourself a facial?
I have an oily "T" zone.
Okay, dude.
Hey, you, uh,
you sent Kristen flowers.
That's right.
You spent a hundred dollars.
That's the limit.
You're screwed.
Actually, I sent the flowers
before the actual date
so technically, technically,
I didn't break any rules.
Thanks for stopping by, though.
Oh, oh, so that's the way
it's going to be, huh?
Yeah, I can break
the rules too.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
Why am I not surprised?
I'm not going to let you
get away with this.
You don't have much choice.
We'll see.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, bye-bye.
Hey! So, just a light layer...?
Yeah, just
here... and there.
Joey got meat sauce
on the banister again.
Yeah, swing music is so out.
Phoebe, he's got to be
in the room for that to work.
What are you guys
talking about?
We were just
talking about the, you know
the Swing Kings
and just wondering
whether, you know,
they were the right way to go.
Yeah, I went to a wedding once
where they had swing music
and, uh, two months later
the couple got divorced.
I'm not saying that there's
any connection here, you know
but they did tell me
that's why they got divorced.
But I love swing music.
Yeah, but the Swing Kings?
You know, they suck so much
that people actually die
at their concerts.
They just stop living.
All I know is, when Monica and
I went to see them, we had fun
and there's another reason, too.
Well, what is the other reason?
I don't want to say.
Well, you have to
because maybe it's stupid.
Well, it's just
while Monica and I
were dancing to them
it was... the first
time I knew that...
you were the woman
that I wanted to dance
all my dances with.
Oh, crap.
( sighs )
So they said our table
will be ready in
just a few minutes.
Oh, great.
Is your back
feeling better?
Oh, yeah, that's fine.
I guess...
the more muscles you have
the more they can spasm
out of control.
Kristen?
Joey.
Hi.
What are you
doing here?
Oh, I like this place, yeah
and technically, technically
I'm not breaking
any rules, so... you know.
Uh, Ross, this is Joey.
Joey... Ross.
Hi.
Hi. It's nice to meet you.
Yeah. I used to have
a friend named Joey.
I don't anymore.
Our table will be ready
in a couple of minutes.
Yeah, so...
Sure. I would love
to wait with you guys.
Thanks.
So, Joey, um, you look familiar.
Are, uh... are you
on TV or something?
Well, Joey doesn't like
to talk about it
but he's one of the stars
of Days of Our Lives.
That's right. That's right.
Don't you play a woman?
A woman in a man's body.
Much better.
So, you know, Ross, it's funny
'cause you
look familiar to me, too.
Have you ever been married?
Why, yes, yes, I have.
In fact, um...
just the other day
Kris and I were talking
about how I've been married
and how I have a son.
Yeah. Little Eric.
That's right. Wait. No, Ben.
So you've just been married
the one time then?
Well, um...
You've been married twice?
Yes
and...
another time after that.
Boy, I'm
getting hungry.
Uh, hey, Joey
have you ever been
so hungry on a date
that when the girl
goes to the bathroom
you eat some of her food?
You said the waiter
ate my crab cake.
( laughing )
Yeah. So, uh, Ross, that, now..
why did that
first marriage break up, hmm?
Was it because
the woman was straight
or because she was a lesbian?
Do you two know each other?
No.
No, no.
It just seems like Ross
is the kind of guy
who would marry a woman
on the verge of being a lesbian
and then push her over the edge.
Wait a minute.
Were you on a poster
for gonorrhea?
Have you ever slept
in the same bed with a monkey?
Hey! You leave Marcel
out of this!
Fine. Have you ever got stuck
in a pair
of your own leather pants?
Hey, hey, have you
ever locked yourself
in a TV cabinet, VD Boy?
Monkey lover!
Where do you think we lost her?
Probably around gonorrhea.
Hi, honey, I'm home!
MONICA:
Don't come in here!
Why? Do you have another
boyfriend in there or something?
No. We only mess
around at his place.
You know, it's funny.
I started it, but now
it's scaring me
so could you
come out here, please?
No, I'm wearing
a wedding dress.
Oh, you got a wedding dress?
That's great.
Yeah, but I'm
not keeping it.
Well, then, why can't I see it?
Oh.
I guess you can.
Okay, but I-I have
to return it
so you can't like it.
Okay, I promise,
I'll-I'll hate it.
Wow, you, you look...
hideous.
Really?
Yeah, that's like the most
ugliest dress I've ever seen.
Why do you have to return it?
Oh, because it
doesn't really fit.
Oh, by the way, I...
I booked the Swing Kings.
Oh, that's great. Great. Thanks.
But that dress,
I mean, it's like, ugh.
It's terrible. It makes me want
to just rip it right off you.
Okay.
But you can't rip it.
Well, maybe a little.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
You want to look at the song
list for the wedding?
Guys?
I thought you were
going to be gone all day.
All right, what's going on?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I-I should probably
leave you girls alone.
Yeah, laugh
all you want
but in ten minutes we're going
to have younger-looking skin.
Yeah.
You know, she could use
a little ( whistles ).
I was going to say.
Oh, nice shot! Yeah!
Hoop! Hoop! Hoop!
Yeah!